I'm not Heo Dong Jin.
Dad!
No!
Tae Jeong, come out!
No! It's dangerous!
Sir, please help save my dad.
We found the body of a 40-year-old male
inside a car at Dongcheon Reservoir.
Immediate support requested at the scene.
Don't go.
Please.
What should I do? I must have lost my mind.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you for yesterday.
So what was all that about?
It was during a heavy rainstorm
that my dad's body
was found in the reservoir.
Ever since then, every time it rains heavily,
I sometimes feel overwhelmed.
By the way, can you answer
what I asked you yesterday?
Why did you come to this house?
I want you to be honest with me.
Proof. I came to find proof.
Proof?
Ever since my brother
left home to meet Heo Dong Hwa,
he never came back.
What?
My brother lent Heo Dong Hwa
a large sum of money.
Then you should have
reported it to the police.
Why did you come here yourself?
How do I know you're not lying right now?
I did try to report it.
But they just said
that most cases like this are simply runaways
and told me to wait for him.
So you broke in
and pretended to be a family member?
I think Heo Dong Hwa
is involved in my brother's disappearance.
Dong Hwa wouldn't do something that bad.
Just because you knew him a certain way
doesn't mean that's all there was to him.
What? Why are you here?
Didn't you say you left?
Kang Chul Jin?
I guess Dong Hwa came back, huh?
Not really.
But I got a message.
[Tae Jeong, I just saw your text
because I'm abroad.]
Tae Jeong, I just saw your text
because I'm abroad.
I don't think it's a good idea
that you stay at my house, sorry.
Abroad?
By the way, what are you doing here so early?
I was worried about Dong Hwa.
Am I not allowed to come?
Didn't Dong Hwa call you?
Nope, I haven't heard a thing.
Ah, by the way,
you said you were here with Dong Jin, right?
Tell me more about that.
- Why?
- Why else, you idiot?
Gotta catch the impersonator.
You didn't believe me.
At the time I didn't,
but I've thought about it,
and you have no reason to lie to me.
Plus, I found out this idiot Dong Hwa
had money problems.
So maybe someone holding a grudge
impersonated his family or something.
Anyway, that weirdo isn't here now.
Tell me. What did he look like?
Actually, there was no one.
Ah, darn it! What kind of crap is this?
Are you saying you lied?
Yeah, man.
Seriously?
I just wanted to mess with you,
since I haven't seen you in a while.
Can I come in?
Why do you want to go inside?
Well, what if something happened to Dong Hwa?
I gotta take a look.
He texted me, though.
Then why hasn't this punk reached out to me?
Show me that text.
I don't have my phone on me.
Good, you can show it to me inside.
Where are you, Heo Dong Hwa?
Bet this punk's passed out again somewhere.
How long has he not come home?
Last time we texted was 4 or 5 days ago.
Ah, look at this fancy stuff.
Did you buy this?
Huh? Yeah.
Were you planning to eat all this yourself?
Are you on a staycation or what?
Why are you trying to check the bedroom?
Get out of my way.
No one's really here.
I told you, it was a joke.
Not here either. Come on, this is so lame.
Thought you were hiding
a secret lover or something.
Stop saying nonsense.
Nonsense?
You've forgotten your place, Tae Jeong.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
You crybaby.
Oh, dear.
This is really comfy, huh?
Nice place you got, eh?
Anyone might believe
that your family is still rich.
Come on now, show me the text.
Huh? Yeah.
I'm worried, too,
but looks like he's doing well.
Hey, you punk.
He told you to beat it.
Why did you crawl back in here?
Well... my funds are a bit tight lately.
You pathetic loser.
You should've tried saving up.
Darn it!
Why didn't that punk say where he was going?
I should get going.
Is this yours?
Huh? Yeah.
Nice.
Give this to me.
Huh?
I was just kidding, man.
If you hear from Dong Hwa, let me know.
Don't go off on your own.
When did I do that?
You idiot.
You miss evidence right in front of you.
What?
I'm leaving. See you later.
I'll go wash up.
Aren't you hungry?
Not in the mood.
Your stomach seems to be.
The eggs look a little burnt?
I know.
How could you mess up frying eggs?
It's the pan. It doesn't work.
- If you don't like it--
- It's okay. I'll eat it.
What?
Why did you hide me?
I wasn't hiding you.
You're lying.
You saw me.
Sorry for deceiving you.
As soon as I find proof,
I'll get out of here.
Do it in two days.
I'll need to leave too by then.
- Thanks.
- Hold on.
You probably misunderstood Dong Hwa.
He's a good person.
How can you be so sure?
I know him.
He's my closest friend.
But what kind of proof are you looking for?
Heo Dong Hwa has a secret phone.
A phone shouldn't be that hard to find.
But it hasn't turned up yet.
Must be hidden real well.
This house is like a maze.
Lots of hiding spots too.
I'll help you look for it.
No need.
It's my job.
You need to find your family, right?
Dong Hwa's passport?
So he was lying that he's abroad.
No way...
Did he text me here,
pretending to be Dong Hwa?
[Tae Jeong, I just saw your text
because I'm abroad.]
Why bother impersonating Dong Hwa?
Where did you go?
I had some quick errands to run.
Is something wrong?
What's that sound?
It sounds like it's coming
from outside, right?
I need to go take care of something.
Get some rest.
What is he trying to hide?
Why did he tell me to stay away,
pretending that Dong Hwa had gone abroad?
If he's just looking for a phone,
why go this far?
What if there's a bigger secret
I shouldn't be here for?
No way...